（圣埃斯特感化院 加州 1996年）
熄灯
Lights out!
克莱图斯 你在吗
Cletus. Are you there?
我的天使
My angel.
这是给你的
This is for you.
医生怎么说
What did the doctor say?
他说突变进化了
He said the mutations are advancing.
我的能力太强大
My powers are too strong.
克莱图斯 我好害怕
Cletus, I'm scared.
不会有事的
It's gonna be okay.
他们要来把我抓走
They're coming to take me away.
把我送去一个有我这种人的地方
They're sending me to a place where there are others like me.
他们不能这么做
They can't do that.
我不能失去你 你是我的一线希望
They can't take you from me. You're my one bright light.
我会永远爱你
I will always love you.
法兰西丝
Frances!
放开我
Get off!
法兰西丝
Frances!
不
No!
（旧金山警局）
（墨里根）
有任何遗言吗
Any last words?
欢迎来到你的新家 法兰西丝
Welcome to your new home, Frances.
（雷文克劳夫精神病院）
（现今）
（克莱图斯·卡萨迪会被判死刑吗）
你的男友终于罪有应得了
Your old boyfriend's finally getting what he deserves.
没有他的世界会更安全
And the world will be a safer place without him.
《毒液2：屠杀开始》
墨里根警探 恕我直言
Detective Mulligan, with all due respect,
我不想去见克莱图斯·卡萨迪
I don't want anything to do with Cletus Kasady.
没办法 他只想见你
Well, that's too bad, because he only wants to see you.
上次你有机会问他话却搞砸了
In my opinion, you had your chance with Kasady and you blew it.
对啦 他现在想怎样
Right. So, what does he want?
也许他想说出找不到的尸体在哪儿
Maybe he wants to spill the beans about where the missing bodies are buried.
所以你这次得套出他的话
So you're gonna have to do the right thing for a change.
不 把你的臭手拿开
No! Take your tiny hands off of me!
我们应该当人民保母 吃掉坏人
We should be out there, protecting the city. Lethally!
你在干什么
What was that?
放开我
Unhand me!
当一个人想要飞就不能逼他在地上爬
Man should never consent to crawl when he has the impulse to fly.
你是个低能失败者
You are a bottom-feeder.
给我闭嘴
Be quiet.
我说过多少次我在工作的时候
How many times have I told you that I want you to hide yourself.
你得乖乖躲起来
when I am working?
我是讲真的 你得尊重我
I am serious. It is important. You have to show me respect.
- 尊重 - 对
- Respect? Respect? - Yes! Yes.
- 好吧 - 很好
- Okay. - Okay.
- 卡萨迪会向你爆料 对吧 - 对啦
- Kasady gonna give you the scoop, right? - Right.
- 错了 - 什么意思
- Wrong. - What do you mean?
因为你搞砸了一切
Because you blow everything.
我明白了 你又在说安妮
Okay, I see. You're talking about Anne again.
我想念她
I miss her!
- 我会去 - 我不喜欢你
- I will do it. - I don't like you.
让我吃他
Let me eat him!
你不配得到好东西
You do not deserve nice things.
（圣昆丁监狱）
欢迎回来 艾迪布洛克
Welcome back, Eddie Brock.
我常常想到你
I've been thinking about you.
你想怎样 克莱图斯 找我来干嘛
What do you want, Cletus? I mean, why am I here?
帮一个被关这么久的人
Do a man who's buried alive.
一点小忙 好吗
a kindness, won't you?
传达一个信息给我广大的…
Get a message out to all my…
粉丝群
fans…
为了报答你
and in return,
- 我会给你我的人生… - 什么
- I'll give you my life… - What?
故事
story.
听说你最近工作不是很顺利
I heard the written word hasn't been working out so well.
像这样的独家报导
Piece like this, an exclusive…
会让你谷底翻身
would put you back on top.
继续说
Go on.
大家都爱…
People love…
连环杀人魔
serial killers.
我所有的秘密
All my secrets.
全都告诉你 艾迪
laid bare, Eddie.
这么多的屠杀
So much carnage.
为什么找上我
But why me?
我喜欢你
I like you.
好吧 一言为定
All right, it's a deal.
你的信息是什么
What's your message?
遥远的大教堂…
"That distant cathedral…
是我目中一切
is all I see…
折翼的天使…
fractured angel…
是另一个我
the other part of me."
刊登在你的专栏
Print that in your column.
就这样 你要谁看到
Is that it? Who's gonna read that?
一首随性的俳句
Some random haiku?
刊登出来…
Print it…
我的…
and what's mine…
就是你的
is yours.
哇 我真幸运
Lucky me.
再见 艾迪
Goodbye, Eddie.
谢谢你
Thank you.
大混蛋一个
What a dick.
艾迪 快看
Eddie, look. Look.
- 你在干嘛 - 帮你调查啊
- What are you doing? - Your job for you.
（于苦难中努力奋斗）
艾迪
Eddie.
别忘了我 艾迪
Don't forget me, Eddie.
得到什么线索
What did you get?
我得了头痛可能还有肺痨
I got a headache and probably got tuberculosis.
什么 大声点
What? A little louder.
他念诗给我听
He read me poetry, man.
你把这当笑话吗 我笑不出来
Is this some kind of joke to you? Because I'm not laughing.
你这结屎脸应该笑一笑
Yeah, you could do with a laugh.
拜托 这种事得花点时间 好吗
Come on, man. These things, they just take a little time. All right?
- 你挖到什么消息… - 当然
- The second he gives you something. - Of course.
马上告诉我 别害我出糗
Keep me ahead of the curve, Eddie. Don't embarrass me!
明白吗
Do you understand?
相信我
Trust me.
今天我只会挖到两球巧克力脆片冰淇淋
The only scoop I'm getting today is double chocolate chip.
不要 我的脑会冻僵
No! I get brain freeze.
给我过来
Come here.
你看
Look.
- 我在看啊 - 拿两支奇异笔
- I'm looking. - Grab those.
拿了
All right.
好吧
Okay.
现在…
Now,
你觉得怎样
what do you think?
- 我是毕加索 - 不是啦
- I think I'm Pablo Picasso. - No!
- 好吧 - 过来 仔细看
- Okay. - Come here. Look.
你看到什么
Well, say what you see.
- 一栋房子 - 算了
- It's a house. - Never mind.
这个我知道 是一棵树
Oh, I know this one! It's a tree!
白痴 坐下来
Idiot! Sit down.
现在…
Now…
专心点
pay attention.
宾果
Bingo.
哇靠
Holy cow.
（加州罗迪欧海滩）
你和克莱图斯·卡萨迪的友情
Would you say your friendship with Cletus Kasady.
帮你解开这几十年的谜团吗
is what allowed you to solve this decades-old mystery?
你是外面世界唯一跟他说过话的人
You are the only person from the outside world he's spoken with.
看来他喜欢你
Seems he likes you.
他是个连环杀人魔 不会喜欢任何人
Well, you know, he's a serial killer. I don't see how he can like anyone.
（号角日报）
布洛克挖出警方查不出的线索
Brock was able to uncover what the FBI and police could not.
为平息众怒
Bowing to public outrage,
加州州长推翻他的暂缓行刑决定
the governor of California has overturned his moratorium.
重新下令对卡萨迪执行死刑
and reinstated the death penalty for Kasady.
布洛克也像是被打了强心针
Brock's career's been given a much-needed revival,
再度咸鱼翻身
putting him back on top once more.
这场痛苦的折磨终于要结束
A harrowing story finally comes to an end.
受害者得以安息 家属也获得宽慰
Vindication for the victims and closure for the families,
多亏了一个人的努力不懈
thanks to the diligence of one man.
谢谢你 艾迪布洛克
Thank you, Eddie Brock.
还有毒液
And Venom!
我们可以同心协力
You know, this could be us, Eddie.
行侠仗义、破解悬案
Going out there, solving cases.
打击犯罪 让我吃坏人
Fighting bad guys. Maybe I eat them.
然后拯救世界
And then we save the day.
可是我们已经做到了
But we saved the day. It's done.
你说我可以吃坏人
You said I could eat bad guys!
又是这件事
This again?
我需要自由
I need to be free!
海风吹拂着发丝 光着脚踩上细沙
Feeling the wind in my hair and the sand between my toes.
- 你又没有头发 - 你都没在听
- You don't have any hair. - You are not listening to me.
我有在听
Oh, I'm listening.
我不能继续过这种生活
I cannot live like this anymore!
- 我饿扁了 - 吃掉他们啊
- I'm starving! - So eat those guys.
不行 桑尼和雪儿是好麻吉
I can't. Sonny and Cher are best friends.
真假 太扯了 有够瞎…
Are you serious? That's ridiculous. That's what…
老兄 你出手太重了
Man, that was abusive.
太超过了
That was abuse.
那电视贵得要命
And that's a $2000 TV.
你要学会控制攻击性
You have got to get control of your aggression.
所以才有史努奇
That is why we have Snookie!
我不能只吃鸡和巧克力
I cannot live on chicken and chocolate alone.
我需要吃大脑
I need brains!
鸡也有大脑
Chickens have brains.
这我完全不能苟同
I most passionately disagree.
你看 看看这两个白痴
Look. Look at those poor idiots.
脑子超小的
Small brains.
拜托 又不是它们的错
Come on, man, it's not their fault…
谁叫你非得吃笨憨慢…安太岁
that you live on the old phenylethyla. Laphenylethylan…
- 苯乙胺 - 我是那么说啊
- Phenylethylalanine. - Yeah, I just said that.
我跟你说过很多遍了
I've told you a thousand times,
只有大脑和巧克力才会有
because it is only found in brains and chocolate.
我知道啦 给我听好
That's right. Well, how about this:
你住在我的身体就要遵守我的规则
You live in my body, you live by my rules.
我会住在你的身体是因为我别无选择
I live in your body because, unfortunately, I don't have many options.
那这样好了
Well, how about this, son?
FBI还在调查我们
The FBI is still investigating us.
因为我们涉及的那一堆事件
for all of that stuff that "we were involved with."
要是又有一颗脑袋被吃掉
So if one more head goes missing,
我们会被抓去外星人秘密基地
we will get hauled off into Area 51.
他们会杀了我们 所以我得扛起责任
They will kill us both. So somebody has to be responsible.
责任…
Responsibility.
是庸才的借口
It's for the mediocre.
（混蛋）
- 食物 - 闹够了没
- Food! - Can you stop doing that?
- 食物 - 别再闹了
- Food! - Please just stop doing that.
别闹啊 我有交稿期限
Come on, stop doing that! I have a deadline! Will you stop it?
该死的 好啦
Goddamn it! Fine!
- 晚安 艾迪 - 嗨 陈太太
- Good evening, Eddie. - Hey, Mrs. Chen.
晚安 毒液
Good evening, Venom.
它跟你问好
He says hi.
- 巧克力还没到货 - 不
- Chocolate hasn't arrived yet. - No!
不行 我们说好的
Oh, no. We have a deal.
会怎样 你不保护我了吗
What's gonna happen? You gonna stop protecting me?
想都别想
I don't think so.
我乖乖闭嘴 喂饱你的小秘密
I've been keeping my mouth shut, feeding your little secret.
哇 陈老太太原来是个老江湖
Little old Mrs. Chen is a little old blackmailer, huh?
我不老 我才39岁
Less of the old. I am 39.
- 那我就是今城武 - 没错
- And I am Barry Manilow. - Right.
我很乐意吃陈太太
I am happy to eat Mrs. Chen.
不行 你不能吃陈太太
No, no, you cannot eat Mrs. Chen.
什么
What?
我猜只好用B计划了
I guess it's gonna have to be plan B.
B计划是什么
What's plan B?
又要吃鸡喔
Not this again!
我需要吃人脑才能活
I need human brains to survive.
抓几只鸡就快闪吧
Now, pick up some chickens, man. Let's go.
我吃够了恶心的土鸡
I'm done with this grossness.
看看我们能做多威的事情
Look at all the amazing things that we can do!
我们在白白浪费才华
We are wasting our talent.
坏人
Bad guy!
哈啰 小猫咪
Hello, kitty!
放了他…放了他…
Leave him. Leave him be. Leave him be! Leave him be!
- 我要咬下你的脑袋 - 不准
- I shall remove your head. - No, you won't.
- 用来当保龄球 - 不行啦
- I will use it for bowling! - No, you will not!
我要用来…
I will take it to.
- 我们喜欢哪一家保龄球馆 - 七星
- What is the one that we like, Eddie? - It's Lucky Strike.
- 对 - 把他放下来
- Yes! - Put him down.
我要带你去七星保龄球馆
Lucky Strike. I will take you to Lucky Strike.
- 打出300分的完美比赛 - 不行
- And I will score a 300-point game. - You won't.
把你剩下来的小肥宅身体留在这里
The rest of your pudgy little boy body will be left here,
泡在恶烂的馊水里面
rolling around in dumpster juice.
天啊
Oh, God.
不 放下来
No! Put him down!
不不不
No, no, no! No! No!
好啦
Fine!
她不需要我们的帮忙
She didn't want our help.
她不知道她需要我们帮忙
She did not know she needed our help, Eddie.
这不一样好吗
There is a difference.
是安妮
It is Anne!
安妮打来了 艾迪
Anne is on the phone, Eddie!
- 嗨 安妮 - 嗨 艾迪
- Hey, Anne. - Hey, Eddie. Hi.
- 嗨 - 对她好一点
- Hi. - Be nice to her.
你好像在喘气 我没打扰你吧
You sound out of breath. I'm not catching you at a bad time, am I?
没有啊 我只是在…
No, no, not at all. I'm just.
我只是在瞎晃
I'm just hanging around.
抱歉我没回你电话 我猜…
I'm sorry I haven't returned your calls. I guess…
我只是需要一点空间
I just needed a little space after the whole…
在外星人咬掉人头的事以后
alien-biting-a-guy's-head-off thing, so…
昔日的好时光
The good old days.
我有事要告诉你 能不能见个面
Anyway, so I have some news, and I was wondering if we could meet?
- 好耶 - 好啊 那会很…
- Yes! - Yeah, sure, that would be.
那会很赞 棒呆了
That would be fine. Great.
- 好 明晚如何 - 明晚
- Okay, great. How's tomorrow night? - Tomorrow night?
- 好啊 - 晚上八点
- Yeah. Great. - 8:00?
- 芝茱餐厅 - 好
- L'Araignée? - Okay, great.
- 我很期待 - 我也是 拜
- Looking forward to it. - Me too. Bye.
- 好 - 她跟医生分手了
- Great. - It's over with the doctor!
听起来就是个被狠甩的妹子
That is the voice of a woman who just got brutally dumped.
别闹了
Stop!
你不想看起来超帅
Don't you want to look your best?
别烦我 你老是爱念我
Just leave me alone. You are always nitpicking.
哇
Wow.
嗨
Hey!
嘿
Hey.
好了 嗨
Okay. Hi.
尴尬癌上身
Awkward.
怎样 毛先生好吗
So how's it going? How's Mr. Belvedere?
很好啊
Good, good.
他还是用地毯擦屁股 学你的
He's still wiping his ass on the carpet. He learned that from you.
是啊 法律援助的工作如何
Yeah. How's the legal aid work going?
你知道我最爱帮助弱者
You know how much I love an underdog.
是啊 所以你才忍受我这么久
Yeah, that's why you put up with me for so long.
你自己说的
You said it.
所以…
So.
所以
So?
不晓得 我觉得应该亲自跟你说…
I don't know, I thought it would be better to tell you in person that…
不
No!
哇 安妮 那真是…
Anne. Wow, that is…
比我送你的那枚钻戒大很多
That is so much bigger than the one that I got you.
超浮夸的
It's gaudy.
- 丹 对吧 丹医师 - 对 是丹
- That's Dan, right? Dr. Dan. - Yeah, it's Dan.
哇 安妮 好样的
Holy shit, Anne. Way to go.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
- 我很好啊 - 我不好
- Yeah, I'm okay. Yeah. - Well, I am not okay.
你可以说 恭喜 我很为你开心
You could just say, "Congratulations, I'm happy for you."
互相关心的两个人可以说谎
You know, like two people who still care enough about each other to lie.
好让对方没有罪恶感
so that the other one doesn't feel like complete shit.
也许我们也能这样
Maybe we could do that version of this?
- 我很为你开心 安妮 - 屁啦
- No, I am happy for you, Anne. - No!
恭喜了
Congratulations.
谢谢你
Thank you.
新郎原本是我们 艾迪
That was going to be us, Eddie!
我就很希望丹过马路被车撞飞
I, for one, would not be inconsolable if Dan were to fall into traffic.
脑袋、脚和牙齿都被撞掉
and lose his head and his feet and all of his teeth!
- 什么 - 你说什么
- What? - What was that?
什么 没事
What? Nothing.
我问你问题
If I ask you a question,
你可以实话实说吗
do you have the ability to tell me the truth?
你是说为你订婚觉得超开心吗
You mean, as in being super happy for you because of your engagement?
因为你刚叫我说谎 这样很矛盾
Because you just told me to lie, so that's really confusing.
毒液也在吗
Is Venom with you?
它死了
He's dead.
是啊 我现在心死了
I am. I'm playing dead right now.
我是说它…
Yeah, I mean, he…
对啦
Right.
- 好吧 - 好吧
- Okay. - Good.
那真是…
Well, that's…
你不会变 对吧
You just don't change, do you?
你在说什么 我惊呆了
What are you talking about? This is just a huge shock.
安妮 我爱你 我得花时间消化
Anne, I'm in love with you. This is a lot to process.
其实你没能力爱任何人
The truth is you don't love anybody. You can't.
更无法做出承诺
Commitment's just not your thing.
好吧 好吧
All right, then, fine.
别嫁给丹
Do not marry Dan.
丹给我安全感
Dan makes me feel safe.
你让我觉得像坐云霄飞车
And you made me feel like I was on a roller coaster.
总有一天要下车
Sometimes you have to know when to get off.
- 只要不吐就好 - 不要吐
- Yeah, and not yak. - And not yak!
你明白吗 不要吐
You know? Not yak.
恶心
Yak.
毒液 好好照顾他 好吗
Hey, Venom. Take care of him, all right?
别让他搞砸一切
Don't let him keep messing everything up.
我要逼你哭 艾迪 她会很感动
I'm going to make you cry now, Eddie. She will love it.
哭啊 哭啊
Cry. Cry.
我得慢慢消化
It's a lot to process.
恭喜了 安妮
Congratulations, Anne.
这是好消息
That's great news.
（限速30）
慢点 兄弟
Slow down, pal!
为什么 你又不怕出事
Why? You don't believe in consequences.
受了伤你会治好
No injuries. You fix them.
喝醉了你让我清醒
No hangovers. You mend them.
我想受伤都不行
I couldn't even hurt myself if I tried!
艾迪 很抱歉我治不好你的伤心
Eddie, I apologize that I can't mend the heart.
情伤的打击又更大
Emotional pain, it hits much harder.
持续得更久
And it lasts longer.
你只能像个大人咬牙忍住
You just need to pull up your big-boy pants and take it.
你说得倒容易
Yeah, well, that's easy for you to say.
为什么
Why?
因为我是真的人
Because I'm a real boy.
你只是个变形虫
And you're just an amoeba.
我们刚失恋所以不跟你计较
I will only take that because we are hurting right now.
放心兄弟 我会陪你走出情伤
Don't worry, buddy. I will get you through this.
你知道什么让我早上元气满满吗
Do you know what always cheers me up in the morning, Eddie?
香肠和大脑
Sausages. And brains!
我说要 我说要
I say either And I say either.
我说都不是 也不是 也不是 都不是
I say neither Neither, either, either, neither.
让我们结束这一切吧
Let's call the whole thing off.
土豆泥
Potahtoes.
我喜欢西红柿 我喜欢西红柿
I like tomatoes And I like tomahto.
土豆 土豆泥 西红柿 西红柿
Potatoes, potahtoes Tomatoes, tomahtoes.
让我们结束这一切吧
Let's call the whole thing off.
开心点 老兄
Cheer up, old pal!
而且
And, oh.
如果我们结束这件事
If we call the whole thing off.
我们必须分开
Then we must part.
这是寄给你的
That's for you.
（圣昆丁监狱死囚牢房）
你跟一只蚂蚁当笔友
Are you pen pals with an ant?
喂 你听听
Listen to this.
亲爱的好麻吉
"Dearest pally pal,
我诚心诚意邀请你见证
I hereby invite you to witness.
我的…死亡
my demise,
我临终的一刻
my final moments.
也就是我活在被称为地球的
on this spinning shit wheel.
这颗烂星球
that we call Earth."
你得负责任
You are responsible.
你把克莱图斯·卡萨迪害死
for bringing about the end of Cletus Kasady.
所以才应该在我离开时替我开门
It's only right that you hold the door for me on my way out.
我的心跳会停止 就跟我出生时一样
They'll stop my heart, just like it stopped at my birth.
要是小克莱图斯·卡萨迪没被救活呢
What if Cletus Kasady had never been revived?
他就不会把外婆推下楼梯
He would never have pushed Grandma down a flight of stairs.
拜拜外婆 你这个老太婆
Bye-bye, Grandma, you puckered old sphincter.
他也不会把吹风机丢进妈妈的浴缸
He would never have thrown a hair dryer into Mother's bathtub.
是的 妈妈 我是个坏男孩
Yes, Mama, I'm a bad, bad boy.
他也不会被老爸打个半死
He would never have been beaten to the brink of death by Daddy-o.
然后被送去…
And sent to…
圣埃斯特少年感化院
St. Estes Home for Unwanted Children.
那像地狱的马戏团…
That circus of hell…
只有一线希望
with one bright light.
噢 艾迪
Oh, Eddie.
我们都是伴随着鲜血和痛苦出生
We are all born into this world through blood and pain.
每一个英雄都有一个起源故事
Every hero has an origin story.
你的朋友…
Your friend…
克莱图斯·卡萨迪
"Cletus Kasady.
亲抱亲抱…
Kiss, hug, kiss, hug.
笑脸
Smiley face."
疯子
Nut job.
- 我应该去的 - 那是个馊主意
- You know, I should be there. - No, it's a bad idea.
这都是我造成的
I mean, I put him there.
是他活该 谁叫他要当个疯狂杀人魔
Actually, he put himself there when he decided to be a complete lunatic.
登登
Ta-da!
你能挺我会很赞 就这一次
You know, it would be nice just to have your support, just for once.
蕃茄酱
Ketchup?
这地方是吃到饱餐厅
This place is an all-you-can-eat buffet.
谁鸟我吃掉几个脑残白痴
Who's going to care if I polish off a couple of these idiots?
你不知道谁是好人
You can't be sure who is and who is not guilty, buddy.
他们在坐牢
They're in prison!
对 但有些人被冤枉
Yeah, but some people take false confessions.
或被迫认罪 我们看过谋杀犯的形成
You know, they take pleas. We watched Making a Murderer.
- 没事吧 - 没事 只是在练习
- You all right? - Yeah, man, I'm just practicing.
我是个掠食者 艾迪
I am a predator, Eddie.
- 狮子才不吃色拉 - 你又不是狮子王
- Lions do not eat salad! - But you're not a lion, are you?
你比较像猪狗或蝙蝠
I see you more of a vexatious little pig-dog-house-bat thing.
好吧
That's fine.
- 你很讨厌 - 你才讨厌
- You suck. - You suck!
- 你说什么 - 抱歉
- Excuse me? - Yeah, wow.
我没有借口 只是恐慌症发作
I don't have an explanation for that. I think I'm having a panic attack.
我在这里签到
Yeah, I'll sign here.
站在牢房两呎外 不准碰囚犯
Stand two feet away from the bars. No touching the condemned.
了解
Understood.
访客来了
Visitor's here!
这是我的事 不是我们的事
This is a "me" thing, not a "we" thing.
什么都是你的事
Everything is a "you" thing.
今天算你走运 艾迪布洛克
Happy day for you, Eddie Brock.
我要向你爆料
What a scoop.
魔幻悲惨之旅的终点站
The end of the Magical Misery Tour.
我担心你的灵魂
I worry for your soul.
害死一个人怎么对得起自己的良心
How will you live with the weight of snuffing out a man's life?
我就是来跟你请教的
I was hoping maybe you could give me a couple pointers.
你很爱搞笑 对吧
Funny little guy, aren't you?
用不着 我的记忆超好
Don't need that. My memory is outstanding.
没礼貌
Rude.
有因就有果
Consequences.
你做的每一个决定
Every decision you ever make.
我们弃谁于不顾 以何种姿态离去
Who do we leave behind, and how do we leave them?
空荡荡的…
A connubial bed,
婚床
empty.
在黑暗中苦等
Waiting in the darkness.
不会来临的救援
for the rescuer who never comes.
都是因为你
Because of you.
这家伙在胡说八道
This guy makes zero sense.
你跟我是同类
You and I are the same.
不 并不是
No. No, we're not.
内心扭曲 恶劣的父亲
Twisted insides, mean daddies.
你给我回家的感觉 像家人一样
You feel like home to me, Eddie. Like family.
说真的 我在这世上只想要一样东西
And really, truly, that is all I ever wanted in this world.
家庭
Family.
那你真的不该杀死你外婆和妈妈
Killing your grandmother and your mother sure is a funny way of showing it.
你想说出什么事 趁你还没…
Anything you wanna unburden yourself with before…
被处死之前
this happens?
有的
Yes.
我想为你许个愿
I have wishes to bestow upon you.
噢 他人真好
Oh, that is kind.
我希望你…
I want to wish you…
和我一样心痛
this heartbreak.
糟糕 太迟了
Too late.
我希望你孤零零地过一生
I wish for you to see out your days alone,
就像你一直以来这样
as you always have been.
说话小心 老兄
Watch it, pal!
你到底想要什么
Where are you going with this?
你害惨了每个爱过你的人 艾迪
You are a cancer to everyone who ever loved you, Eddie.
欺骗信任你的未婚妻
Deceived your trusting fiancée.
怪不得你老爸从不再看你一眼
And no wonder Daddy could never look at you again.
你害死他老婆 就是你老妈
after you killed his wife, your mother,
因为她难产而死
just by being born.
你这王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
不 不要
No, no! No, no, don't! Don't!
不准你这么跟我麻吉说话
Speak to my friend again like that! I dare you!
喂喂
Hey, hey!
不准碰囚犯 你给我退后
No touching the inmate. Hey, back up!
艾迪
Eddie?
你得走了
You're done.
我尝过人血的味道 那绝对不是
I have tasted blood before, my friend, and that is not it.
艾迪布洛克有个大秘密
Eddie Brock has a big secret!
闭嘴 卡萨迪
Shut up, Kasady!
- 那可能是个错误 - 闭嘴
- That may have been a mistake. - Shut up.
你不是艾迪布洛克吗
Hey, aren't you Eddie Brock?
我也不知道
I don't know anymore.
- 艾迪 - 我不想再听你碎碎念
- Eddie! - I don't wanna hear another word.
- 艾迪 - 我不想听
- Eddie. - I don't wanna hear it.
艾迪 对不起
Eddie, I am sorry.
那是他最后一次接受采访
That was his last time on record ever!
他没提到死在他手下的受害者
There's no more words for his victims. You know, they're gone.
也没说出尸体的下落 永远都不会知道
Any clues of outstanding bodies, we've lost forever.
我不是故意的
I didn't mean to.
- 你不是故意的 - 我也道过歉
- You didn't mean to? - And I said I'm sorry!
你不是故意的 但你还是做了
You didn't mean to, but you did it. You just decided, I don't know:
连想都没想过
That's it. You did it.
我们可能会被抓或被杀吗
You didn't even think we might get caught, get killed?
你才懒得想 你只想吃鸡
You don't think about things like that. You think about chickens.
你只为自己想 想你要什么
You think about you, you think about what you want, and you think about you.
让我提醒你 我来之前你是失败者
Let me remind you of something, Eddie. You were a loser before I came along.
连屁都不是 我让你特别
You were nothing. I made you special!
你让我特别 让我告诉你
You made me special? Let me tell you something.
你来之前我有人生 没有鸡 但有梦想
Before you came along, I had a life. I didn't have chickens, but I had dreams.
还有漂亮的未婚妻和超夯的节目
I had dreams and a fiancée and a really successful TV show!
你却彻底毁了那一切
But you destroyed all of those things by yourself.
但我东山再起 努力过活 晚安
Yeah. But you know what? I rebuilt my life and now I just wanna live it. Good night.
你是怎么东山再起的
And how did you build this new life?
你说什么
Excuse me?
谁在墙上找到线索 让你当大英雄
Well, who found the clue on the wall so you could be this big, shiny hero?
谁找到线索 谁
Who found the clue? Who?
没错
Yeah.
不不不 我才不想当什么大英雄
No, no, no. This is not about being a hero for me, man.
我只想平静地生活 你明白吗
This is about wanting to live in peace. Do you understand what I'm talking about?
你根本就不明白
No, you don't understand what I'm talking about.
我不想跟你一起住
Okay, this is about me wanting to live without you.
因为你老是跟我吵着要吃坏人
whining in my ear all the time about eating bad guys.
碎念安妮的事
or nagging me about Anne,
砸烂我的公寓 毁了我的人生
or destroying my place or destroying my life!
你知道我选上你有多幸运吗
Do you know how lucky you are that I chose you?
你选上我
You chose me?
大哥 是我收容你耶
Buddy, I'm the only person that took you in.
你朋友把你赶出狗屁星球
when your friends kicked you off the planet Ming Mong.
因为你是废物 你是贱民
because you are a reject! You are a pariah!
保护我个屁 你什么也保护不了
Lethal protection, my ass. You couldn't protect anything.
没用的东西 连洗马桶都不配
You are useless. You couldn't get a job down here cleaning toilets!
抱歉 我不是故意的
I'm sorry! I don't know what came over me.
让我治好你 我再捶你一次
Please, let me fix it.So I can break it again!
你这个王八蛋
You son of a bitch!
出去 拿着你的东西 滚
Out! Get out. Take your stuff. Get out!
这是我家
This is my house!
不
No!
小声点
Keep it down up there!
滚出去
Get out!
桑尼
Sonny?
- 你不敢 - 我当然敢
- You wouldn't dare! - Yeah, absolutely.
不不不
No, no, no!
- 好耶 - 不
- Yeah! - No!
我要报警
I'm calling the police!
真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.
现身吧
Show yourself.
你赢不了的
You can't win!
看看我 再看看你自己
Take a look at me. Look at the size of you.
小废物
Puny.
好大的胆子
How dare you?
我猜要说拜拜啰
I guess this is goodbye.
好耶 我们终于有了共识
Oh, yeah. Finally something we agree on.
搞什么东西 太扯了吧
What in the world? All this crazy shit.
好耶
Yeah!
不 不
No. No.
不不不
No, no, no.
不
No!
好耶
Yeah!
不
No!
- 好耶 - 不
- Yeah! - No!
噢耶
Oh, yeah!
不
No.
不不不
No, no, no.
我希望从没遇见你
I wish I never met you!
再见
Sayonara!
克莱图斯·卡萨迪 你受到加州政府
Cletus Kasady, you have been tried, convicted.
审判、定罪并判决处以死刑
and sentenced to death by the state of California.
愿你的死能还给受害者家属公道
May your passing bring closure to the victims' families.
也愿你在来世获得平静
And may you find peace in the hereafter.
暴乱将至
Soon come chaos.
至死方休
Chaos soon come.
那是你的遗言吗
Are those your final words?
享受这场秀吧
Enjoy the show.
典狱长
Warden.
邪恶即将降临
Something wicked this way comes.
让我出去
Let me out!
别动
Don't move!
喂
Hey!
饶了我
Please.
我有个家庭
I got a family.
典狱长 有遗言吗
Any last words, warden?
不 求求你
Don't! Please!
圣昆丁监狱 愿你燃烧殆尽
San Quentin, may you rot and burn in hell.
你们全下地狱 但我仍活着
May your walls fall down And may I live to tell.
变成一个更聪明更强大的人
I walk out a wiser, stronger man.
典狱长 你吃起来像火腿
And, warden, you tasted just like ham.
（严禁吃人）
你们俩被驱逐了
You two are being evicted.
别用哀怨眼神看我 本来就行不通
Come on, don't look at me like that. It was never gonna work out.
好吗
All right?
好耶
Yes.
他冲得太快 进攻锋线拦不住他
Just because of how quickly he moved in, the offensive line cannot pick him up.
连环杀手克莱图斯·卡萨迪正在潜逃…
Breaking news. Serial killer Cletus Kasady is on the run…
操
Shit.
全州展开追捕行动
…as a state-wide manhunt is underway…
噢 靠
Oh, shit.
他昨晚从圣昆丁监狱大胆逃狱
…after last night's audacious escape from San Quentin.
- 嗨 - 你没死喔
- Hey. - What, you're not dead?
没啊
No.
- 能进去吗 - 可以啊 请进
- May I come in? - Yeah, sure. Come on in.
我也是刚刚看新闻才知道
I was just seeing for myself on the news.
要我说 这糟糕透顶了
Yeah, on a scale of one to ten, it's 11 bad.
是啊
Yeah.
来自圣昆丁的消息比扯铃还扯
Reports coming from San Quentin are, quite frankly, bananas.
电视很赞
Nice TV.
他怎么逃出去的
How did he do it?
他怎么逃出去的 真是个好问题
Yeah, how did he, indeed? That's the million-dollar question.
你是他的特别访客
And yet again, you were his special visitor.
- 他跟你说什么 - 我 什么都没说
- So, what did he tell you? - Me? Nothing. Nothing at all.
没提到越狱计划
Nothing about an escape plan?
打扮成怪物逃出去
Nothing about some kind of elaborate breakout costume?
没有
No.
你怎么每次都被卷入这种事
Well, how come every time you seem to be at the center of these things,
却什么都不知道
and then miraculously you know nothing about it?
也许我很幸运
Maybe I'm lucky.
最好是
Yeah, right.
你说…
You said…
来自圣昆丁的消息很扯
the reports coming out of San Quentin are bananas.
是什么意思
What do you mean by "bananas"?
你采访他那天我问过类似的问题
Remember when I asked you a similar question the day you interviewed him?
情报就是力量
Information is currency.
你应该最清楚
You of all people should know that.
少来了
Come on.
我以为他会来找害他被处死的人
I thought he'd come to try to find the man that nearly got him executed,
但我猜错了
but I guess not.
你最好低调点
I'd lay low if I was you.
我自己出去
I'll see myself out.
好吧 努力想
Okay, think. Think, think, think.
毒液会怎么做
What would Venom do?
他会先找到你吃掉你的脸 靠
He would find you before you find me, and he would eat your face! Damn.
好吧
All right.
我们弃谁于不顾 以何种姿态离去
Who do we leave behind, and how do we leave them?
- 空荡荡的婚床逐渐腐朽 - 婚礼
- A connubial bed, empty, left to rot. - Connubial. Is it marriage?
在黑暗中苦等不会来临的救援
Waiting in the darkness for the rescuer who never comes.
我不懂
I don't understand.
- 层层地狱… - 山丘的教堂一片死寂
- "That circle of hell…" - The cathedral on the hill is fell silent.
都是因为你
because of you.
你跟我是同类
You and I are the same.
只有一线希望
"…with one bright light."
内心扭曲
Twisted insides…
希望
Bright light.
你给我回家的感觉 像家人一样
You feel like home to me, like family.
圣埃斯特感化院
St. Estes.
（化装舞会 表演嘉宾小席姆兹）
太弱了
Crapola!
又一个不行的
Another one bites the dust.
看看这些怪咖
Look at all these weirdos.
我的同类
My kind of people.
超赞的装扮
Nice costume.
嘿
Hey!
帅喔
Awesome work!
最赞的装扮 我的天
Greatest costume ever! Oh, my God.
日本货吗
Is that Japanese?
不 我自己做的
No, I made it myself.
- 嗨 - 谁 我
- Hey! - Who, me?
你好 猛男
Hello, gorgeous.
抱歉 不是我的菜
Sorry, no, not my type.
我从艾迪的衣橱出柜了
I am out of the Eddie closet!
好炫的车子
Hello, darling.
赛车红 我喜欢
Racer red, got to have it.
我们来开趴吧
Let's get this party started.
哇 好耶
Oh, hell, yes.
停车 停车
Stop! Stop, man! Stop! Stop!
该死
Shit.
- 你是真的 - 没错
- You are real. - I am.
杀了我的母体毒液 我们将所向无敌
And once I kill that thing that made me, we will be indestructible.
我知道它在哪儿
I know where to find him,
但你要先帮我找回失去的东西
but first I need you to help me find something I lost.
一言为定
Deal.
噢耶
Oh, yeah!
老兄
Dude.
帅喔兄弟 怎么样
Oh, yeah, bro! What?
谢谢大家
Thank you!
我靠
Oh, shit.
你的装扮太棒了
Your costume is amazing!
谢谢那个人
Thank you, one person!
艾迪是错的
Eddie was wrong.
他觉得我丢脸 把我藏起来
He kept me hidden because he was ashamed!
但现在看看我 你们爱我
But look at me now! You love me.
我自由了
And I'm free!
耶
Yeah!
别再虐待外星人 那不好
Stop this cruel treatment of aliens. It is wrong.
我们应该都能在这颗星球和平共处
All of us should be able to live together upon this ball of rock.
自由自在地做自己
Free to be who we be!
我爱你
I love you!
我也爱你
I love you too!
好耶
Yeah!
致命守护者丢麦
Lethal Protector out.
哇 这场面很难接
Well, that was a hard act to follow.
真希望你今晚看到我…
I wish you could have seen me tonight…
艾迪
Eddie.
（克莱爱法兰）
妈的
Holy shit.
- 墨里根 - 我是艾迪布洛克
- Mulligan. - It's Eddie Brock here.
希望也许不大 但我可能找到线索
Look, this may be a long shot, but I think I may have found something.
说吧 你找到什么
Go on, Eddie. What do you got?
我上次去见卡萨迪时他提到婚床
Last time I spoke to Kasady, he was talking to me about connubial beds.
还有婚礼 当时我有听没懂
and marriage, and it didn't make a whole lot of sense to me.
但我在圣埃斯特找到了线索
But I'm here at St. Estes, and I found this…
我站在一棵树前面
Well, I'm standing in front of a tree.
上面刻了几个字
And I'm looking at it. It's got a carving on it.
克莱爱法兰
It says, "CK loves FB."
我在想他可能正在去找这个法兰
I'm thinking that maybe whoever this FB is might know where he's headed.
也许你能传些档案给我
And if you can, I don't know, pull up some files from St. Estes,
查出这个法兰是谁
maybe you can figure out who this FB is.
那是法兰西丝巴瑞森
FB, that's Frances Barrison.
哇 好快
Wow, that's quick.
不可能的 艾迪
Yeah, it's impossible, Eddie.
她挂了 我杀了她
She's dead. I shot her.
我能效劳吗
Can I help you, sir?
你有网络吗
Got any of those Internets?
（法兰西丝巴瑞森遭到击毙）
（警方报告 最高机密）
（转至雷文克劳夫精神病院）
你还活着
You're alive.
等我出去
When I get out,
要剥掉你的脸皮 戴着去派对
I'm gonna slice your face off and wear it to a party!
你永远出不去 席格菲
You're never getting out of here, Siegfried.
谁也出不去
No one does.
法兰西丝
Well, Frances.
你男友耍了一招逃脱术
It seems your sweetheart has done a Houdini.
逃出圣昆丁监狱
act over there at San Quentin.
今天的大新闻
It's all over the news.
噢 别太兴奋 他找不到你
Oh, don't get excited. He's not gonna find you.
死贱货
Screw you.
多谢夸奖
How flattering.
但你不是我的菜
But you're not my type.
不知道他在哪里
I wonder where he could be.
我就在这里
I'm right here.
登登
Ta-da!
嗨 宝贝
Hi, baby.
我不想吓到你 好吗
I don't want you to freak out, okay?
但我要你见见…
I'd like you to meet…
屠杀
Carnage.
超性感的
That is so hot!
快上
Go.
66年野马
A '66!
我的梦想车
My dream car.
我记得啊 看看你的技术
Yeah, I remember. Let's see what you got.
好耶 宝贝
Yes, baby!
旧金山警局 投降吧
This is SFPD. Stand down!
够了 你会害死它
Stop! You'll kill him!
她敢再尖叫 我就啃掉她的脸
She does that again, I'll eat her face.
它对声音很敏感
He's sensitive to sound.
停车 投降
Stop the vehicle! Stand down!
谁说爱情已死
Who said romance was dead?
喂 酒鬼不准进来
Hey! No drunks in here!
救救我 食物
Help me. Food.
滚 给我滚
Out! You get out!
巧克力
Chocolate.
毒液
Venom?
我很难让他们站起来 陈太太
I'm having trouble keeping them standing, Mrs. C.
艾迪呢
Where's Eddie?
食物
Food…
怪物
Monsters!
到处都是怪物
Monsters everywhere!
到处都是
They're everywhere!
怪物
Monsters!
（法兰西丝巴瑞森）
发出通缉令 设下警戒线
Put out an APB, form a perimeter,
封锁州界
blockade state lines,
把布洛克带来
and bring in Brock.
我帮不了忙 只会浪费你的时间
I'm no use to anybody here. I'm just wasting your time.
知道我怎么想吗
You know what I keep thinking? I keep thinking:
艾迪还有什么卡萨迪的事没说
"What else is Eddie Brock not sharing about Cletus Kasady?
他为什么要艾迪去看他的死刑
Why was it Eddie that Cletus wanted to witness his execution?"
扯上你就会发生坏事
Bad things happen around you.
你的公寓去年死了好几个人
Multiple dead bodies at your building last year,
你在龙虾餐厅的奇怪行径
that bizarre outburst at the lobster restaurant,
火箭爆炸时只有你在生命基金会
and only you at the Life Foundation when that rocket exploded.
现在鸳鸯大盗会合了
And now Clyde's found Bonnie.
精神病院的医生挂了
and there's a dead psychiatrist at a facility.
我今天才知道
I knew nothing about until today.
大家都说他们看到怪物
And people are talking about seeing monsters.
怪物
Monsters?
怪物是什么意思
What do you mean "monsters"?
怪物 克莱图斯去哪这怪物都跟着他
Monsters, Eddie! Everywhere Cletus goes, so goes this supposed monster.
天啊
Oh, God.
快说 艾迪
Talk to me, Eddie.
给我说实话
Talk to me.
他是怎么做到的
How's he doing it?
秘密是什么 他怎么能制造幻觉
What's the secret? How's he making people see things?
好吧
All right…
我得打通电话才能回答你的问题
I can't answer any more of your questions without making my phone call.
我会让你打电话
I'll get you your phone call.
但你知道秘密会怎样吗
But you know what secrets want, Eddie?
一定会被揭露 很难保守秘密
They want out. That's why they're so hard to keep.
艾迪要你这么做
Eddie asked you to do this?
没人能帮他吗 我们迟到了
He has no one else that can help? We'll be late for the party.
他惹上麻烦 丹
He's in trouble, Dan.
麻烦老是找上他
Yeah, trouble is his thing.
- 又会有外星人 - 当然不会
- Are there gonna be aliens again? - No, of course not.
我想单独跟他说话
I'd like to speak to him alone.
有人受伤你就不能替你的当事人说谎
Your duty of honesty supersedes your duty to the client if somebody gets harmed.
法学院没教你吗
They teach you that at posh school?
嘿 安妮 多谢你赶来
Oh, hey. Anne. Hey, Anne, thank you so much for coming.
那矮冬瓜真会碎念
Boy, that little guy's a charmer, huh?
你惹上多大的麻烦
How much do I need to worry about you right now?
我搞砸了
I messed up.
多糟糕
Okay. How badly?
糟透了 都是我的错
It couldn't be worse, and it's all on me.
不管是什么 你都得说实话
Whatever you did, you just need to tell the cops the truth.
我不能说他们在追捕的连环杀人魔
No. No. No, I can't tell them that they are chasing a serial killer.
身体里头有一个外星人
who's also got an alien inside of him.
而且它会展开大屠杀
and he's capable of killing everybody.
毒液 告诉我这是怎么回事
Venom. Talk to me, what's happening?
它不在 它不在这里
No, he's not here. He's not here.
你是在说谎 还是它真的不在这里
Is this like an I'm lying "He's not here" or is this a real "He's not here"?
它不在这里
He's not here.
天啊 艾迪
Jesus Christ, Eddie.
- 圣埃斯特起火 - 搞什么
- St. Estes fire. All units. - What the actual fuck?
艾迪 动动脑筋
Eddie, think.
我只知道它不吃东西跑不远
I don't know. All I know is that he can't go long without eating food, right?
而且它只吃鸡和巧克力
So he's eating chicken and he eats chocolate and that's it.
它守规则的话就只能吃那些
And that is only if he's still observing the rules.
我们得找到它
We need to find him.
你是说我得找到它
You mean I need to find him.
对啦 你得找到它 我再跟它和好
Yeah, you need to find him, please. And then I will fix it.
- 我试试看 - 谢谢你
- I'll try. - Thank you.
陈太太
Mrs. Chen.
- 是谁啊 - 是我
- Who's asking? - It's me.
你要什么
What do you want?
- 她讲话够呛 - 听好
- She's a charmer. - Okay, listen.
你伤了艾迪的心
You broke Eddie's heart.
我没空解释那是大错特错
I don't have time to explain why that's off the mark.
毒液在哪里
Do you know where Venom is?
你也想伤它的心
You wanna break his heart too?
我不想讨论谁对谁做了什么
I'm not gonna get into who did what to who.
艾迪说它可能会来吃巧克力
Eddie said he might be here for the chocolate.
我只需要跟那外星人说话
I need to speak with the alien.
你说不会有外星人
You said there wouldn't be any aliens.
- 不会有更多 - 新闻快报
- I meant more aliens. - Breaking news.
市长发出宵禁令
The mayor has issued a curfew…
麻烦开大声点
Turn the volume up, please.
卡萨迪和巴瑞森应被视为
Kasady and Barrison should be treated as.
携带武器和极度危险
armed and extremely dangerous.
今晚警方持续追捕行动
An all-out manhunt continues tonight.
所以呢
So?
- 克莱图斯身上有个共生体 - 我的天
- Cletus has a symbiote. - Oh, my God!
你还有什么瞒天大谎没说
Any other information you're pathologically lying about?
- 孬种 - 什么
- Pussy. - Excuse me?
- 艾迪需要毒液 - 她骂我孬种
- Eddie needs Venom. - She just called me a pussy.
它说它不需要他 没有他活得更好
He said he didn't need him, that life was better without him.
我不懂你干嘛这么在乎…
Okay, I don't understand. What do you care?
噢 等等
Oh, wait a second.
你快给我出来
You get out here right now.
看到没
Do you see that?
- 真的啦 看到没 - 有啦 看到了
- Seriously, do you see that? - Yeah, hon, I've seen it.
艾迪这混蛋得一个人去打怪
Eddie's going to have to fight this battle all by his little bitch self.
别幼稚了 去帮你朋友
Don't be a big baby. Go help your friend!
他说我连洗马桶都不配
He said I couldn't get a job fixing toilets!
克莱图斯会去找他 没有你他会死
Cletus will come for him. He won't survive without you.
当然啰 因为我才是大英雄
Of course he won't. Because I am the hero of the two of us.
是啊 你是性感大英雄
Yeah, you're the big sexy hero.
你最酷 你最猛 你最威
You're the coolest, you're the hottest, and you're the bravest.
是啊
I am.
我就站在这里耶
I'm still standing right here.
没人喜欢你 丹
No one likes you, Dan!
我超爱你大显身手
I love seeing you in action.
我们去救那个大混蛋吧
Let's go save that asshole.
我保证我们从此就会自由了
I promised we'd be free from here.
我们要走进山丘上的大教堂
And we'd walk to the cathedral on the hill.
- 一场婚礼 - 三个客人
- A wedding. - Three guests.
一人带一个客人
One for each of us.
射瞎我眼睛的警察
The cop that took my eye.
艾迪布洛克
Eddie Brock.
还有毒液
And Venom.
血色的婚礼
A red wedding.
你没找到它
You didn't find him?
天啊 发生什么事
Oh, my Lord. What happened?
嗨 丹 我们走吧
Hey, Dan. All right, let's go.
我才不跟他讲话
I'm not talking to him!
- 它不想出来 - 什么意思
- He doesn't want to come out. - What do you mean?
克莱图斯要屠城 我们得快走
We have to leave now 'cause Cletus is gonna wipe the city out.
他不道歉我们什么都不会做
We're not doing shit until he apologizes.
它只要你道个歉
So he's looking for an apology.
我知道你不喜欢认错
I know that amends aren't your thing.
它现在要我道歉
Like, as in right now, an apology?
我要他跪求我
I need him to beg.
好吧 我要当个大人
Fine, I will be the bigger of us.
我才是大人 不过继续说
I will always be the bigger of us. But go on.
- 它说什么 - 它说它在认真听
- What is he saying? - He said he's listening very sincerely.
好吧 听好 我很抱歉
All right, listen to this. I am sorry.
不够诚恳
Not the right tone.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不够
Nope!
对不起啦
I am sorry!
太奇怪了
So weird.
对不起
I'm sorry!
我不知道你干嘛对我大吼
Why are you shouting at me?
好吧 我遇到你之前是个失败者
Okay, well, fine. I was a loser before I met you.
对啊 没错
Yup. That's right.
现在的我不一样了
And now I am someone.
你让我变得很特别
You made me special.
没错
Damn right!
- 再加码道歉 - 加码 好吧
- Why don't you put a cherry on it? - A cherry on that? Right.
我
I'm…
我真心为我所说的一切
I am truly very sorry for everything that I said,
没说的一切和做的一切
everything that I did not say, everything that I did,
和我没做的一切向你道歉
and probably everything that I did not do.
它在考虑
Yeah, he's thinking.
拜托
Come on, come on.
好吧
Okay!
噢不
Oh, no.
亲下去
Kiss her!
你现在要亲我吗
Are you gonna kiss me now?
- 不要 - 不要
- No! - No?
我不会再那么做了
God, I'm never doing that again.
也许吧 老实说 超好玩的
Well, maybe never. I don't know. Honestly, it's really fun.
拯救世界就能自称致命守护者吗
If we save the day, can we call ourselves the Lethal Protector?
太老派了
That is so '80s.
丹 快打包走人 有必要…
Dan. Pack quickly. Don't stay. And if for any reason.
- 火与噪音 - 火与噪音是乐团吗
- Fire and sound. - "Fire and sound"? Is that a band?
那会杀死他们
No, it's what kills them.
好吧 放心 我会罩她
Okay, look, man, I've got her.
我不会道歉
Not sorry!
天啊 真是抱歉
God, I'm so sorry.
那一对很需要伴侣咨商
Those two need some serious couples counseling.
我正开到布洛克住处
I'm pulling up to Brock's now.
靠 我的天
Shit. Oh, my God.
卡萨迪 把手举高
Kasady, place your hands on your head!
哪一只…
Which…
手
hands?
搞什么
What the fuck?
找到你了
We found you.
尖啸会很高兴
Shriek will be so pleased.
香喷喷的布洛克
Brockalicious!
闪闪惹人爱
Bling-a-ling.
你该套进哪只手指
Now, whose finger were you meant for?
小小鱼儿的闪亮亮诱饵
A nice shiny lure for a little fishy.
好了 来吧 毛先生
Okay, here we go, buddy.
你好 安妮 我掐昏了你男友
Hello, Anne. I just incapacitated your boyfriend.
他不会有事
Now, he'll be okay,
只要你说出艾迪布洛克在哪
with an answer about where Eddie Brock is.
我才不会告诉你
Well, I'm sure as shit not gonna tell you that.
很可惜我得伤害你
It's a shame to hurt you.
告诉布洛克…
Tell Brock.
（婚礼 恩典座堂）
克莱图斯要来个交换
Cletus will make a swap.
她的头换他的头
Her head for his.
他会杀死你们俩
He's gonna kill you both.
很多人试过
Peeps have tried that already.
都搞砸了
Botched it!
他们找不到他
They can't find him!
他们也在追杀我们
They are hunting us too, buddy.
快啊 你在哪
Come on, where are you?
丹 怎么回事
Hey, Dan. What's going on?
- 他们抓走她 - 什么
- Eddie, they got her. - What?
- 他们抓走安妮 - 冷静点
- They've taken Anne! - Calm down.
带她去他们的婚礼
They took her to their wedding.
- 哪儿 - 他们的婚礼
- They took her where? - Their wedding.
- 恩典座堂 快去 - 这就去
- Grace Cathedral. Hurry. - We're on our way.
看来我们要去一场婚礼
All right, it looks like we are going to a wedding.
- 有点心吃吗 - 当然有
- Oh, will there be canapés? - You bet your ass.
遥远的大教堂…
That distant cathedral…
是我目中一切
is all I see.
折翼的天使
Fractured angel…
是另一个我
the other part of me.
- 各位亲朋好友 - 先送礼物
- Dearly beloved… - Gifts first.
其实传统习俗…
Actually, traditionally.
给我闭嘴…
Shut your mouth…
神父
Father.
宝贝 我有你最想要的东西
Baby, I got for you what you want most.
- 那警察 - 那警察
- The cop? - The cop.
请继续 神父
Continue, Father.
各位亲朋好友
Dearly beloved,
若是有人反对这场婚礼
if anyone objects to this marriage,
请开口 否则就永远闭…
speak now or forever hold their…
她在哪里
Where is she?
你来了
There you are.
你死定了 吾父
Death to you, Father.
不
No!
不是你 神父
Not you, Father.
是你 父亲
You, Father.
靠
Oh, shit!
你去哪 你干嘛
Where you going? What are you doing?
比我想象的糟糕 它是红色的
This is much worse than I thought. That is a red one.
- 红色的 - 我们得马上闪人
- Red one? - We should leave. Immediately.
别管安妮 反正我们不喜欢她
Annie will get over it. We never liked her anyway.
- 走吧 - 现在
- So let's go. - Now?
恭喜这对新人 然后就闪人
Congratulations to the happy couple. We are leaving.
艾迪 哈噜
Eddie!
我马上来 好吗
I'll be right with you. All right?
你得马上出来
You need to come out right now.
现在处境超危险的
Because I am feeling super, super vulnerable right here.
- 布洛克跟你一样 - 很快就不会
- Brock's just like you? - Not for long.
艾迪 给我过来
Eddie, over here!
你得立马出来
You need to come out right now.
我会让你吃很多人 大吃特吃
I will let you eat everybody! You can eat them all!
除了长袍男 不能吃他
Apart from him in the robe. You cannot eat him.
- 打勾勾 - 打勾勾
- Promise? - I promise!
谢谢你
Thank you.
宝贝
Baby!
给我闭嘴
Shut your mouth.
婚姻触礁了
Marriage trouble already?
- 受死吧 - 好样的
- Time to die. - That's the spirit!
我是说我们 我们死定了
I mean us. We are going to die.
我杀了你
I killed you.
鬼是杀不死的
Well, you can't kill a ghost.
你 杀了他
You. Kill him,
但给我乖乖闭嘴
but keep your mouth shut.
我们的老婆知道怎么做
Our wife knows what she's doing.
小声一点
Just turn it down.
你以为你在跟谁说话
Who do you think you're talking to?
- 拦住他 - 死警察
- Stop him! - My cop!
蜜月期结束了
Honeymoon over?
天啊 不
Oh, God. No.
威力提升
Power up.
不
No!
求救…克莱图斯·卡萨迪…
Mayday, mayday, mayday! Cletus Kasady.
他们说以眼还眼是怎样来着
What do they say about an eye for an eye?
火与噪音
Fire and sound!
只是没有噪音
Except without the sound.
宝贝
Baby!
克莱图斯
Cletus!
单挑吧 布洛克
Mano a mano, Brock.
知道我在牢里是怎么过的吗
You know how I spent my endless days?
我都在想你只报导单方面的故事
I spent them thinking about how you only told one side of the story.
完全没提到小小克莱图斯
You didn't write about the part where Cletus was abused.
被父母和外婆虐待
by Mommy, Daddy, and Granny!
你没告诉全世界他是个吓坏的小男孩
You didn't tell the world how he was a scared little boy.
没人在乎他
that no one cared about.
也没人来救他
and no one came to save!
你从没扪心自问…
You never asked yourself.
为什么
why!
你是个蹩脚的记者
That's bad journalism.
太爽了
Oh, happy days.
我不是疯子
I'm not a crazy man,
但我很会记仇
but I am a vengeful one.
你要看着她死
You're going to watch her die.
安妮
Anne!
快想办法
Do something!
艾迪 我们恐怕打不赢他们
Eddie, I'm afraid we cannot beat them.
宝贝 你太超过了
Baby, that's too much.
你得阻止他
You gotta stop him.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我会永远让她闭嘴
I'll shut her up for good.
不 住手 你会杀死她
No! Stop! You're hurting her!
- 起来啊 - 我起不来
- Get up! - I can't.
快看 他们不是共生体
Look, look! They're not symbiotic.
- 离她远一点 - 闭嘴
- Get away from her! - Shut up.
别碰我老婆
Take your hands off my wife!
他们不是一对
They're not a match.
我们才是
We are.
没错 我们是天生一对
That's right. We are.
我们合体后就是…
Together we are…
致命守护者
The Lethal Protector!
展开大屠杀吧
Let there be carnage!
我抱住你 没事吧
I got you. You okay?
父亲 我们其中一个必须死
Father, one of us must die.
我们需要火
We need fire.
或噪音
Or sound.
不
No!
我的天
Holy mackerel!
一点也不好吃
He did not taste good.
我是个杀人魔 不管有没有怪物
I'm a killer with or without the monster, Eddie.
知道我想要什么吗
You know what I really wanted?
不知道 你要什么
No. What was it, Cletus?
我跟你说过 但你没在听
I told you, but you weren't listening.
我现在在听
Well, I'm listening now.
我要你的友情
I wanted your friendship.
抱歉 克莱图斯
I'm sorry, Cletus.
去这家伙的
Fuck this guy!
毒液 快把他带走
You in there, get him out of here.
他们会来抓你们
They're gonna come for you both.
我知道
I know.
嘿 安妮
Hey, Anne.
保重了
Take care.
你也是 英雄
Yeah. You too, champ.
丹
Dan!
- 你也要保重 - 谢了
- You take care too. - Thanks.
我喜欢你
I like you.
不过我们不需要他
We totally didn't need him, though.
老实说 他只会碍事
Honestly, I think he was more of a hindrance than a help.
怪物
Monsters.
那是唐吉诃德 他旁边是桑丘潘萨
That there is Don Quixote, and the guy next to him is Sancho Panza.
他们很不同
They're two very different people.
对世界的看法不一样
who have very different takes on the world.
做事的方法也不同
Different ways of doing things.
有时候根本就不喜欢对方 但…
Sometimes they didn't like each other a whole lot, but ultimately…
他们合作无间 带出彼此最好的一面
they worked together to bring out the best in each other.
艾迪 时候到了
Eddie, the time has come.
我必须一个人去
I must go alone.
他们要的是我
It is me they want.
是啊
Yeah.
亲爱的桑丘
Well, my dear Sancho,
事实是真理的敌人
facts are the enemy of truth.
那是什么意思
What does that even mean?
意思是…
It means…
意思是我们…
It means that we…
是毒…
are Ve…
逃犯
Fugitives!
毒 也对啦
…nom. Yeah. Yeah.
亡命之徒
On the run.
也是啦
That too.
- 谢谢你带我来这里 - 不客气 兄弟
- Thank you for bringing me here. - You're welcome, buddy.
很美吧
It's beautiful, huh?
很抱歉不能让你享受…
I'm sorry that we can't do anything about the old.
海风吹拂着发丝 但…
wind-in-your-hair situation, but…
奥修说过 当你爱一个人
Osho says, when you love someone,
就得接受他们的全部 包括缺陷
you accept the whole person, Osho? With all of their defects.
- 缺陷… - 没人是完美的
Defects. Nobody is perfect.
倒转一下 你刚刚说你爱我
Just go back a minute. You telling me? You just said that you love me.
你有说
You did.
- 我们要去哪 - 我也不知道
- Where will we go? - I don't know. I don't know.
需要致命守护者的地方吧
Anywhere that needs a Lethal Protector, I suppose.
- 你是认真的 - 是啊
- You really meant it! - Yeah.
我们需要披风
We will need a cape.
还有面具
And a mask.
不需要 我们有你 放心吧
No. No, I think you got that covered. We're good.
- 我超爱这部电影 - 是啊
- Oh, I love this show. - Yeah.
麦斯希姆诺的感受都没被顾到
Maximiliano's feelings are not being validated.
那他就不应该偷藏这么大的秘密
Yeah, well, he never should've kept such an insane secret, man.
每个人都有过去 艾迪
We all have a past, Eddie.
你偷藏了什么秘密吗
You hiding stuff from me?
横跨宇宙八百亿光年的知识
Eighty billion light years of Hive knowledge across universes.
会在你的小脑袋瓜里爆炸
would explode your tiny little brain.
那是什么意思
What does that even mean, man?
让我给你看看
Well, let me give you a taste, then.
我们共生体经历过的一点事情
Just the smallest fraction of the things we symbiotes have experienced.
好啊
Okay.
- 好了吗 艾迪 - 好了
- Ready, Eddie? - Yeah.
发生什么事
Oh, what's happening?
噢 不
Oh! No, no, no! No!
那是什么东西
What the hell is that?
噢 那只是条毛巾
Oh, that's just a towel.
我们在哪
Where are we?
- 你做了什么 - 不是我
- What did you do? - It wasn't me.
这个由在下揭露的惊人事实
You better believe this shocking revelation brought to light by yours truly.
提出更多问题
has only raised more questions…
- 这是什么 - 关于彼得帕克的秘密…
- What is this? - About the secret life of Peter Parker…
也就是蜘蛛人 也就是蜘蛛威胁
aka Spider-Man, aka the Spider-Menace.
但别担心 《号角日报》会废寝忘食…
But rest assured, dear viewers, we here at the Daily Bugle won't rest…
那家伙
That guy.
揭露他编织的谎言
…until we've uncovered the truth from his web of lies!
我是J·乔纳·詹姆森
I'm J. Jonah Jameson.
晚安
Good night,
愿上帝保佑我们
and God help us all.
兄弟 你在我房间干嘛
Dude. What are you doing in my room?
我…
I…